SURESH REDDY CHALLA

CUSTOMER SERVICE PROFESSIONAL WITH 7+ YEARS OF EXPERIENCE IN CUSTOMER SERVICE AND HOSPITALITY INDUSTRY.

PROFILE

High competent, creative and motivated, professional with 7+ years of experience in customer service industry. Have always been at the forefront of winning new customers, and supporting customers. Adept at the art and science of convincing customers attaining and retaining a higher increase in customer-base for organizations.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Conflict resolution
Problem-solving
Analytical thinking
Strong communication skills
Decision-making
Networking expert
Collaborative nature

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative Organized Team player Fast learner Motivated

CONTACT

+91 9849845128 <u>sureshr</u>eddychalla@gmail.com

ADDRESS

17-1-391/T/190, Flat Number: 301 Siri Nivas Apts, Saraswathi Nagar Saidabad, Hyderabad.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Looking forward to working at a company that values creativity and which provides opportunities to take excel in my skills, and thereby take my career to the zenith of success and beyond. I am desirous to be with the leaders in business and contribute to the success of business putting to use my years of experience in customer services industry.

EXPERIENCE

CUSTOMER SUPPORT SPECIALIST (TRAVEL CONSULTANT)

Dnata International Pvt.Ltd. | Mar 2017 - Aug 2020

Managing customer calls, dispelling doubts, educating clients about hotel packages, supporting clients as needed, following up with new leads, converting leads into customers, etc.

TEAM LEAD - CUSTOMER SUPPORT TEAM EXPERT

Corporate Solutions Redefined India Pvt. Ltd. | March 2012 - Aug 2015

Managing the team responsible for the customer support services. Guiding team members on resolving issues related to hotel booking, cancellation, refund, etc.Organizing schedules for the team members, improving customer satisfaction through constant

EDUCATION

MASTERS IN TOURISM & HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT

NITHM. affiliated to JNTU | 2008 - 2010

BACHELOR OF HOTEL MANAGEMENT

Global Institute of Hotel Management, affiliated to OU | 2005 - 2008